Darling, Darling!
Sailing
on the
cobalt blue!
The clouds float above the sea!
Hanging out
just me and you!
Our time is now and soon you'll see!
Smile with all your heart as you go
past the problems that await you!
Keep your hopes alive!
Never look down upon yourself!
Just cast a magic spell!
You will get through!
Crazy, crazy rainbow!
Star twinkle twinkle rainbow star!
Fast beats premonitions!
Just like the colors from
all the rainbow beams!
Crazy, crazy rainbow!
Star come with me and we'll go far!
We're just fallen angels!
Shooting arrows into our hopeful dreams!
Crazy, crazy rainbow star!
I'm a crazy rainbow star!
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!
Within the cobalt blue!
Seven colors will come to our surprise!
Crazy Crazy Rainbow Star!
Twinkle Twinkle Rainbow Star!
Abandon all your worries!
Your troubles show through
the mirror of your eyes!
Let me comfort you, my love!
I'll hold your time within my glove!
We sure are fallen angels!
Just singing our hearts
all out from up above!
Dying, dying!
Crazy, crazy, hippo star!
I'm a crazy, hippo star!
All right, then, just to make sure
we're all on the same page about Usopp.
This is about doing what's right.
I know. Let's move.
You've been depressed for long enough.
Shut up!
Why is mine the only one with a drawing?
Who cares about the picture?
You've got a bounty.
Who is this, huh?
Because it's not me!
I thought it was a photo
until you said something.
It was a handsome face again.
All the women in the world
are gonna laugh at me.
Ugh.
That guy lied to me.
He said he was a reporter
for the local paper.
Having a bounty kind of stinks.
But on the upside, the picture
turned out pretty cute.
I fought like a true man back there.
I'm a pirate just like
all the rest of you.
And what do they mean by pet?
I'm a doctor, darn it.
Well, try harder then.
Don't you want to see your ship?
Can't keep our big bro waiting.
I know, I know.
Well, I hope we're not
forgetting anything.
Once we get Franky in our
new ship, we're out of here.
Hey, Sanji's not moving anymore.
Yes, we'll just have to find a new cook.
What?
Just give me a minute, Darren!
Yes, pirate lady!
Can't you stay a little longer?
This is certainly an unusual case.
There may not be many of them,
but every member of their crew
has a bounty on their head.
They're worth over 600
million total. Impressive.
but I was wondering what about
this black-legged character
why is there no photo of him
I well I assure you sir I
did take one but look at what
happened when I developed
the film it's quite unsettling
the photo is completely black
did you by any chance forget
to take off the lens cap
big bro we brought the Straw Hats
big bro where are you they're here i see
something big you think
that's it hey Franky we're
ready for our ship now
oh hey icepots what's up
good to see you yeah you
too but where's Franky
unfortunately Franky can't be here
at the moment but the ship is indeed
complete shall we take a look uh-huh i
think you're going to be impressed i was
floored simply looking at the blueprints
this ship can sail any scene it may
take you to the end of the Grand Line
after all just let me You see it already!
Harry!
There's a message that Franky asked
me to pass on to you, Straw Hat.
He said that if you're going to
be the king of pirates someday,
then your ship should
be the king of beasts!
It's amazing! Say that again!
Oh, wow! How lovely! Oh, yeah!
It's super big and super cool!
It looks ready to break, Star!
And it's really free?
Huh.
It's got to be twice as big as Mary.
Wait, is the sail a sloop?
It's huge! Show me the kitchen!
Hurry, I want to see!
I love the figurehead.
What kind of flower is it supposed to be?
Well, I think he intended
it to be a loyer.
The inside is awesome, too!
The deck has a lawn and so soft!
It might be nice to do
some gardening up here.
Good for a nap, too.
Quick, where's the kitchen?
It must have great mobility
with a gaff sail of that size.
Yes, they call this kind
of ship a brigantine.
Brigantine ships are square-rigged in the
front and have a gaff sail in the back,
like a sloop.
They're quite versatile if the
navigator's up to the task.
Sounds like a challenge.
I love it!
Time to check out the interior!
Oh!
It's got a fridge with a lock,
just like I always wanted!
And look at this oven!
It's huge!
Oh, you're the best, Franky!
You made all my dreams come true!
Hey, Ice Pops, this is cool and
all, but where did Franky go?
We gotta thank him for this.
I'm sorry, but it would appear
that he doesn't want to see you.
Huh?
Straw Hat, you were going to invite
Franky to be your shipwright, weren't you?
Yep.
Wouldn't have it any other way.
Besides, this is his ship, after all.
He has to come.
Then that might be your problem.
You mean he doesn't want to join?
Just the opposite.
Rather, if you invited him,
he wouldn't be able to refuse.
That's why he's hiding right now.
Well, what I'm saying is that he
wants to join you in his heart.
Of course, you can probably
see that for yourself,
looking at all the love and care
he put into building this ship.
Whoa, check it out!
There's an aquarium in here, too!
Wow, it's beautiful!
And he's quite fond of your crew, so
please don't blame yourself for this.
But he believes it's his
duty to stay on this island.
His bond has become the
chain that binds him.
Yeah?
Yes.
Though if you ask me, I think he's
being needlessly stubborn over nothing.
Still, that's how he feels.
So trying to reason with him
would be a waste of time.
If you really want him to go with you,
then your only choice is to use Force.
Since he's not willing to break that
chain, you'll have to do it for him.
Use Force?
And after he was so nice to us,
well, I guess I can give it a shot.
Bro, what the heck are you doing here?
Huh?
Why wouldn't I be here, dumbass?
This is the Franky house, right?
I live here.
Yeah, but...
Are you sure about what
you're doing, big bro?
I mean, you...
you want to sail with the Straw Hats
on that ship you built, don't you?
Huh?
What kind of stupid question is that?
Of course not.
Besides, look at this mess.
What would you do without me when you
lugheads can't even build a house right?
Don't say that.
We just got back from begging the
Straw Hats to take you with them.
Even if it'll be tough
without you, you gotta go.
Damn fools.
Mind your own business.
But they want you to go too.
The Straw Hat crew needs a ship right.
You can't just turn them down.
Give me one reason why I should become
a pirate after all we've been through.
I can tell just by looking at you.
I mean, you should have seen
yourself building that ship, bro.
In all the time we've been together, I've
never seen you smile like that even once.
You were like a new man.
You were doing what you were meant to do.
Big bro.
You knew the Straw Hats were going to ask
you to be their ship
right before they left,
didn't you?
That's why you ran away, isn't it?
But thanks to this, it
doesn't matter anyway!
Should've known.
Guess it was only a matter of time.
Even if you wanted, you
couldn't stay with us anymore.
And even if you don't think
we can make it without you,
we don't want to drag you down!
Maybe you forgot already,
but you people were
dying in a ditch before I
picked you up and made
you what you are today.
If I'm not here, you guys will
probably starve to death in a week.
Daddy's on these!
Whoa!
He took his swim breeze! Yes! Brilliant!
Don't lose him! Put us some hands!
Take the undies and run!
Give me back my breeze!
That's the only pair of those I got!
Everyone's scattered!
Let's go!
Have it your way!
He's coming out for us!
You bastards think our
udundies to beat you!
I can take you down
stark naked if I have to!
Only one of us needs to survive!
We gotta make it to Scrap
Island no matter what!
Get those undies to Straw Hat!
Straw...
Keep heading south and don't
look back! We got this!
There's, there's a pervert!
Frankie's running wild and pantsless!
Ken?
I'll kick your ass naked if I have to!
He's even more indecent than usual!
Whoa, check out the...
Hurry, get the children inside!
Don't let them see the pervert!
Strong right!
You're under arrest, Republican decency!
Surrender immediately!
No!
Can't give up the undies!
The Yagora's ready to go! Good! Move it!
The back streets have
turned into a battlefield.
My legs...
so tired.
I'm done for.
Hey!
Pass them to me! Hurry!
Up here!
It's Straw Hat!
Don't you dare!
Let's see where they go next!
Little turd!
Come back here!
So, how'd you like this
ship? It's awesome!
Haha!
In fact, I think it's the
coolest ship I've ever seen!
Thanks a lot!
Stop!
Iris and I have been chaining! Stop it!
Go to that freak in jail!
Damn straight, it's awesome.
It was made from my super
blooper, it's after all.
I included all your requests.
I hooked it up with my
one-of-a-kind soldier dock system.
Have you had the chance to try it?
Sorry, but not yet!
Well, just you wait, cause
it's gonna blow you away!
What about the fish tank if you catch
fish and dump them in the tank up top?
You'll be able to see him
swim around in the room below.
It's an aquarium in a
dining room all in one
whole crew can meet down
there for a fancy dinner?
And you know you'll always
have fresh fish to pick from.
Just like I promised it's the
best damn ship a man can build
a ship of dreams for both of
us now give me back my dreams!
We're applying to smithereens!
Stop her! Got it!
Look, here he comes!
We're counting on you two for this one!
No problem!
Get back!
What the hell are you trying to do
the Franky family secret weapon?
Hey, cut it out this
has gone on long enough
Hey, are we supposed to
send his undies that way?
Come on, Chumper!
Now come, come!
Franky!
Franky was flying!
Heaven is punishing us!
Careful, he could get up and go wild!
Frankie's naked! Big bro!
Frankie's naked!
This certainly took an interesting turn.
Vergo!
Thanks!
The ship is great!
Just like you said, it's the best!
We'll take good care of it!
Yeah!
I had fun with you guys!
Have a safe trip!
Oh, I hate to break it to you,
but if you want your undies back,
then you're gonna have to join our crew!
I've got to sue you for mental anguish.
Think of the children.
Get out of town.
Give me back my briefs, Straw Hat. Sure.
Join my crew.
What are you, stupid?
I'm not going to be a pirate.
You know, you can keep
those briefs, brother.
Standing before the
crashing waves naked and
proud you wouldn't ask a
lion to put on underwear?
So why a man!
He's showing a hip-haired
bottom loud and proud!
Don't look no try as I
might I can't unsee it.
I was a fool!
His determination is too great!
He's a true man! A hero!
Come on, he's obviously just a pervert!
It might get a little rough,
but shall I lend a hand?
Try dos flu.
Grab.
Robin, what did you do?
Oh, man!
Ow!
You're gonna crush him, Robin!
Don't do it!
She'll tear him off!
She's gonna crush him to bits!
Like little oranges!
Robin!
I still want him to be a man
when he joins us! Lay off!
Just looking at him hurts!
What's going on?
They're not fighting, but
Frankie's in a lot of pain!
That scream!
It almost sounds like someone
is choking a chicken to death!
I know he's a pervert, but gosh!
Everyone knows pirates won't give up on
treasure once they've
set their sights on it.
And now that we have this one
in our palms, so to speak,
I won't let go without a fight.
Come on, I already told you.
I couldn't leave this
island even if I wanted to.
I appreciate the offer, really, but
it just ain't in the cards for me.
Sailing the seas would be great and all,
but there's still a lot of stuff
I have left to take care of here.
That's why I gave the ship to you.
I quit being a shipwright a long
time ago, and I'm not going back.
This is the last ship I'm
building for the rest of my life.
I only had one goal as a shipwright,
and now I've fulfilled it.
I made my ship of dreams.
That's a lie, Franky.
You can say what you like,
but I know the truth.
This isn't the ship of dreams
that you talked about before.
Ship of dreams? That's right.
And my dream doesn't end with blueprints
either, it's much bigger than that.
A ship that will sail with pride
and courage over uncharted waters,
fighting its way through
every battle over every wave.
And when it finally reaches
the ends of the earth,
then it will be my ship of dreams.
One day, I'll design that ship and
hammer the nails with my own two hands.
And when its crew sails, I'll
join as their shipwright.
That way, I'll be there when
the ship reaches its goal.
At the ends of the world, even
if it's beat up and worn out,
I know that my ship will shine brighter
than anything the ocean's ever seen.
What do you think?
Pretty awesome, right, Tom?
Ha! You bet!
And if you ride that sucker
down the Grand Line yourself,
then you'll surpass your master!
It's a pirate blood of yours.
Give me a break.
You're all talk.
A thug like you can't surpass Tom.
Huh? See?
You're resorting to violence already!
Ha!
If you're a man, you do it with gusto!
Yeah, well, my dream is different now.
Your dream?
That's not what this is about at all.
You're not on this island because
of something you have to accomplish.
You're here...
because of guilt.
Ever since that day that Tom was
taken away by the government,
you've blamed yourself for what happened.
It's obvious.
But even before Tom left this
island, he'd already forgiven you.
He had shown you a new path.
For years, you've taken punks from the
inner city streets under your wing.
You've taught them to be dismantlers,
you've worked as bounty hunters,
and you've protected this
island from attacking pirates.
All of this to atone for your sins,
to look after the city that Tom loved,
that Tom was forced to leave behind.
Although, I don't imagine
most people saw it that way.
No, of course not.
Because that's not what
I was doing, not at all!
You loved shipbuilding and you gave it up.
You suppressed your dream
for years and years.
Are you going to do that
for the rest of your life?
Tom has already forgiven you.
I've already forgiven you.
Nothing you do will change that.
This has gone on long enough.
It's time to forgive yourself, Franky.
Live, and follow the dream
you've buried for so long.
What the heck?
A bag!
It's luggage for your trip, bro!
Move it!
We're coming through!
It's the Franky family! Bro!
We love you!
Now you too!
Big bro!
Forgive us!
We didn't want to trick you!
Really! We're sorry! We're sorry!
We'll take any punishment you throw at us!
We aren't smart like you, but we
thought long and hard about this.
And even we know that it's the only way!
Only way, huh?
You guys aren't making
any sense to me You think
I'm better off without
my only pair of briefs,
huh?
Think I'll be better off
with a bunch of pirates?
Well, I don't care what you think.
This is my life, and I
decide what's best for me!
I'm the boss, damn it.
You think I'd be happy living out the
life my underlings planned for me?
You say you thought long and hard, huh?
If you'd really thought about this, you
wouldn't have done it in the first place.
I know we're a pain, but is it wrong
for us to worry about you even a little?
You turned our lives around.
We just want what's best for you.
We just want our big bro to be happy.
Can't you see?
Ain't that sweet?
Damn it, you guys!
Damn it, Robin! Stop it!
You'll pay for this!
It hurts so much!
I can't stop crying!
Oh, Ben!
Wait, you're not doing anything?
I only did it one time.
He's just being a big baby.
How convenient.
Now he has an excuse to cry all he wants.
Huh?
He's faking it? Ah!
Ah!
It hurts so much!
I can't stop crying!
Ah!
Big bro!
I feel your pain bro!
You ain't got a clue how this feels!
Well what do we have here?
Some freak job in his underpants.
I think you just stepped into
the wrong part of town, buddy.
I'm Franky.
Hey, from now on, the Backstreets of
Water 7 will be ruled by me and only me.
Got that?
Yeah, yes, sir.
Big bro!
Good stuff.
Let's hit up the next place.
Wow.
This guy thinks he's too
good for pants. I like it.
Let's have a drink together, pal.
We'll show you the way to the bar.
Just follow us.
Hey, what are you doing?
Let go of us!
It's too early in the day, and you're
too young to be drinking like that.
Take it easy.
If you're really thirsty, I can
show you where to get some cola.
So, that sound good to you?
Big bro!
Oh, I need food.
Anyone who's hungry,
get up and come with me.
Let's run wild.
This is the beginning
of the Ferengi family.
Franky! Franky! Franky! Franky!
Franky!
Franky! Franky!
You guys, are you really
gonna be okay without me?
You taught us how to work together.
We'll make you proud
for as long as we live.
Water Severn will never forget your name.
Yeah, we'll be fine.
Don't cry, bro.
We love you.
No matter how far away you are,
you'll always be our boss
and you'll always be our bro.
That's right.
I can't stop.
Hurry.
Yeah, I know.
we got bad news captain
that stupid grandpa of
yours came back for us
loopy he's got a whole
bunch of Marines on the
other side of the island
getting ready to hunt
us down and take us out
you don't have time to figure that out
just set sail what the damn it
Franky put your underwear on
already geez
well
come
on get on my ship captain's orders your
ship already huh an amateur like you will
probably sinker in less than a week you
got the finest vessel on the sea and no
shipwright That's a real pity for the ship.
I mean, what can I say?
You don't leave me much
choice I got to take
care of my masterpiece
after all so set sail.
I'm joining the crew
Don't cry
Tom, this is it.
I'm leaving the island.
Will you teach me how to draw
up blueprints for one, too?
I know I was a bad student, but
I know I only caused you trouble.
Hey!
Did you guys hear?
Big news from Scrap Heave Island!
Did Tom's workers actually
finish the Sea Train?
But all the same, thank
you for looking after me.
You put together a fine team
of shipwrights, Iceberg.
I'm sure they'll take good care of you.
I'm sorry I've been such
a pain over the years.
Granny Kokoro, Shorty and the Rabbit,
Yokozuna,
all the lively townspeople,
my little sisters,
Sodom, Gomorrah, and all my bros,
I love you guys so much.
I'm gonna super miss
you all put on some pants